Guide to the Office of the Dean, Washington Square College and Washington Square and University College of Arts and Science 1929-1984 (Bulk 1951-1980) RG.19
New York University Archives
- Series II: Additional Dean's Files
  - Degrees Conferred, October, 1976 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Degrees Conferred, February, 1977 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Degrees Conferred, June, 1977 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Degrees Conferred, 1978-1979 (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Degrees, February, 1978 (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Degrees Conferred, June, 1978 (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - Degrees Conferred, February, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - Degrees Conferred, June, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 21)
  - GSAS-Degrees Granted, 1973-1974 (Box 50, Folder 22)
  - Degrees Granted, Academic Year, October-June, 1975-1976 (Box 50, Folder 23)
  - Degrees Granted, 1976-1977 (Box 50, Folder 24)
  - Degrees Granted, 1977-1978 (Box 50, Folder 25)
  - Degrees Granted, October, 1977 (Box 50, Folder 26)
  - Degrees Granted, October, 1977 (Box 50, Folder 27)
  - Degrees Granted, October, 1978 (Box 50, Folder 28)
  - Degrees Granted, October, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 29)
  - Certificates Awarded, June, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 30)
  - Point Count, Spring, 1965 (Box 50, Folder 31)
  - Point Count, Summer, 1965 (Box 50, Folder 32)
  - Point Count, Fall, 1964-1965 (Box 50, Folder 33)
  - Point Count, Spring, 1966 (Box 50, Folder 34)
  - Point Count, Summer, 1966 (Box 50, Folder 35)
  - Point Count, Fall, 1966 (Box 50, Folder 36)
  - Point Count, Spring, 1967 (Box 50, Folder 37)
  - Point Count, Summer, 1967 (Box 50, Folder 38)
  - Point Count, Fall, 1967 (Box 50, Folder 39)
  - Point Count, Spring, 1968 (Box 50, Folder 40)
  - Point Count, Summer, 1968 (Box 50, Folder 41)
  - Point Count, Fall, 1968 (Box 50, Folder 42)
  - Point Count, Spring, 1969 (Box 50, Folder 43)
  - Point Count, Summer, 1969 (Box 50, Folder 44)
  - Point Count, Fall, 1969 (Box 50, Folder 45)
  - Point Count, Spring, 1970 (Box 50, Folder 46)
  - Point Count, Summer, 1970 (Box 50, Folder 47)
  - Point Count, Fall, 1970 (Box 50, Folder 48)
  - Point Count, Spring, 1971 (Box 50, Folder 49)
  - Point Count, Summer, 1971 (Box 50, Folder 50)
  - Point Count, Fall, 1971 (Box 50, Folder 51)
  - Point Count, Spring, 1972 (Box 50, Folder 52)
  - Point Count, Summer, 1972 (Box 50, Folder 53)
  - Point Count, Fall, 1972 (Box 50, Folder 54)
  - Point Count, Spring, 1973 (Box 50, Folder 55)
  - Point Count, Summer, 1973 (Box 50, Folder 56)
  - Point Count, Fall, 1973 (Box 50, Folder 57)
  - Final Point Count, Spring, 1974 (Box 50, Folder 58)
  - Final Point Count, Summer, 1974 (Box 50, Folder 59)
  - Final Point Count, Fall, 1974 (Box 50, Folder 60)
  - Final Point Count, Spring, 1975 (Box 50, Folder 61)
  - Point Count, Summer, 1975 (Box 50, Folder 61)
  - Final Point Count, Fall, 1975 (Box 50, Folder 63)
  - Final Point Count, Spring, 1976 (Box 50, Folder 64)
  - Point Count Summer Sessions I & II, 1976 (Box 50, Folder 65)
  - Final Point Count Fall, 1976 (Box 50, Folder 66)
  - Final Point Count, Spring, 1977 (Box 50, Folder 67)
  - Point Count, Summer Session II, July, 1977 (Box 50, Folder 68)
  - Final Point Count, Fall, 1977 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04227110 9
  - Point Count, Spring, 1978 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Point Count, Summer Session I & II, 1978 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Point Count, Fall, 1978 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Point Count, Spring, 1979 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Point Count, Summer Session, 1979 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Point Count, Summer Registration, Summary, 1964-1978 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Point Count-Summer (Summary), 1963-1976 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Summer Session Point Count By Department, 1973-1978 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - A, 1930-1955 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - B, 1929-1955 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Barasch, Mrs. Frances (Woman Students), 1959 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Dean's Office (Baer), 1941 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Bookstore, 1947-1952 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - C, 1930-1954 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Committee For Technology Center, 1958 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Curriculum Committee II, 1929-1947 (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - D-Prior to 1954, 1934-1954 (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - Dean Baer, 1949-1957 (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - Dean's Cabinet, 1936-1959 (Box 51, Folder 20)
  - E-Prior to 1954, 1946-1953 (Box 51, Folder 21)
  - F-Prior to 1954, 1932-1954 (Box 51, Folder 22)
  - G-Prior to 1954, 1948-1953 (Box 51, Folder 23)
  - H-Prior to 1954, 1935-1954 (Box 51, Folder 24)
  - I-Prior to 1954, 1943-1953 (Box 51, Folder 25)
  - J-Prior to 1954, 1945-1954 (Box 51, Folder 26)
  - K-Prior to 1954, 1932-1954 (Box 51, Folder 27)
  - Dean John W. Knedler, Jr., 1962-1963 (Box 51, Folder 28)
  - Dean John W. Knedler, Jr., 1946-1960 (Box 51, Folder 29)
  - Future Proposals Sent to Dean Knedler, 1960-1961 (Box 51, Folder 30)
  - L-Prior to 1954, 1936-1954 (Box 51, Folder 31)
  - Library-Society for the Libraries, 1938-1961 (Box 51, Folder 32)
  - M-Prior to 1954, 1937-1953 (Box 51, Folder 33)
  - Mc-Prior to 1954, 1947-1951 (Box 51, Folder 34)
  - Modern Language Exam, 1929-1941 (Box 51, Folder 35)
  - N-Prior to 1954, 1931-1954 (Box 51, Folder 36)
  - NYU's Program for Leadership and Service in the Sixties, undated (Box 51, Folder 37)
  - President Newsom, 1957-1961 (Box 51, Folder 38)
  - O-Prior to 1954, 1947-1952 (Box 51, Folder 39)
  - P-Prior to 1954, 1931-1953 (Box 51, Folder 40)
  - PT and S, 1939/1940 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04227111 7
  - Q-Prior to 1954, 1940-1949 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - R-Prior to 1954, 1931-1954 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Rapid Advancement Program, 1959 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Recommendations, 1947-1961 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Registration Report, 1947-1957 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - S-Prior to 1954, 1939-1954 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - S-Prior to 1954, 1931-1954 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Self Study Committee, 1955 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Dean's Still, 1958-1960 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Survey Committee, 1937 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - T-Prior to 1954, 1931-1954 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Television and Radio, 1957-1960 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Tenure-Committee On, 1938-1939 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Testing and Advisement-New Forms, 1948-1962 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Tutorial (Dean Cullen), Summer, 1958-1959 (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - U-1954 and Prior, 1934-1952 (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - Undergraduate Scholarship Committee, 1947 (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - V-1954 and Prior, 1932-1952 (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - VA Data, 1946 (Box 52, Folder 20)
  - VA Data, 1944 (Box 52, Folder 21)
  - W-1954 and Prior, 1929-1959 (Box 52, Folder 22)
  - Y-1954 and Prior, 1929-1953 (Box 52, Folder 23)
  - Z-1954 and Prior, 1935-1947 (Box 52, Folder 24)
  - AAVP, 1972 (Box 52, Folder 25)
  - Annual Report of the Dean, 1970-1971 (Box 52, Folder 26)
  - Comm, Law School Recommendations, 1970 (Box 52, Folder 27)
  - Codes for Educational Institutions, 1972 (Box 52, Folder 28)
  - Doctorate Records File, 1973 (Box 52, Folder 29)
  - EEPC, 1970-1971 (Box 52, Folder 30)
  - FAC Meetings, 1970-1971 (Box 52, Folder 31)
  - GNY Campaign, 1970-1971 (Box 52, Folder 32)
  - General Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 52, Folder 33)
  - Graduate School Alumni, 1971 (Box 52, Folder 34)
  - History Department, 1970-1973 (Box 52, Folder 35)
  - MAAS Essay, 1972 (Box 52, Folder 36)
  - Miscellaneous, 1971 (Box 52, Folder 37)
  - Recommendations, 1970-1973 (Box 52, Folder 38)
  - Student Faculty Advisory Committee, 1971 (Box 52, Folder 39)
  - University Admissions, 1971-1972 (Box 52, Folder 40)
  - University College, 1970-1973 (Box 52, Folder 41)
  - Alumni Newspapers, 1972-1977 (Box 53, Folder data_value_missing_50aef083c9ff8afd23c527c17823f377)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04227471 5
  - Cutler, Max, 1967-1968 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Dansforth Foundation, 1964-1975 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Dansforth Literature & Annual Reports, 1970-1974 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Da Ponte, Marcia, 1975 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Data Processing Unit, 1968-1969 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Chee Davis, 1970 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Dean's Advisory Group, 1974-1975 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Outgoing correspondence, 2000 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Dean's Council Minutes, 1969-1970 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Dean's Council French Study in France, 1970- (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Dean's Council Visiting Committee, 1972- (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Dean's Council Dean's Lecture Series, 1968- (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Deans Council Minutes/Agenda's, 1974-1976 (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Dean's Council Minutes, Agenda, Notes, 1975-, undated (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Dean of Faculty of A & S, 1973- (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Dean's List, 1967-1970 (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - Deanship, WSC, 1968- (Box 53, Folder 19)
  - Dean, Vera, 1961-1967 (Box 53, Folder 20)
  - Debate Team, 1963-1966 (Box 53, Folder 21)
  - Degree Candidates; Graduates, 1971-1972 (Box 53, Folder 22)
  - Degree Program, Three -year, 1971-1972 (Box 53, Folder 23)
  - Ad Hoc Committee on Discipline, 1968-1976 (Box 53, Folder 24)
  - Discipline Policy, 1947-1970 (Box 53, Folder 25)
  - Discipline Policy, 1968-1969 (Box 53, Folder 26)
  - Senate: Discipline Procedures, 1968-1969 (Box 53, Folder 27)
  - Disciplinary Panel Hearings, 1974 (Box 53, Folder 28)
  - Student Disciplinary Proceedings at NYU (adopted by Senate 11/12/1970) (Box 53, Folder 29)
  - Disruption, 1968-1970 (Box 53, Folder 30)
  - Student Disorders: Analysis, 1969 (Box 53, Folder 31)
  - Distinctive Roll, 1963 (Box 53, Folder 32)
  - Doctoral Council, New York State, 1974-1975 (Box 53, Folder 33)
  - Distiguished Professorships, 1964-1968 (Box 53, Folder 34)
  - Dow Chemical Corporation, 1968 (Box 53, Folder 35)
  - Draft, 1973 (Box 53, Folder 36)
  - Draft Classification, 1967-1968 (Box 53, Folder 37)
  - Dress, 1964 (Box 53, Folder 38)
  - Dramatic Literature, 1967-1975 (Box 53, Folder 39)
  - Dreyfuss, Camille & Henry Foundation Proposal, 1975 (Box 53, Folder 40)
  - Drugs, 1971 (Box 53, Folder 41)
  - Dual Major, 1967 (Box 53, Folder 42)
  - Duplication of Courses, 1969-1974 (Box 53, Folder 43)
  - E miscellaneous, 1964-1969 (Box 53, Folder 44)
  - Education Policy Committee Reports, 1963-1967 (Box 53, Folder 45)
  - Education Professions Development Act, 1965-1970 (Box 53, Folder 46)
  - Early Decisions at NYU Medical, 1973 (Box 53, Folder 47)
  - Economics, 1966-1975 (Box 53, Folder 48)
  - Enviromental Science and Engineering Group, 1969 (Box 53, Folder 49)
  - Econmics Brochure, 1975 (Box 53, Folder 50)
  - Evening College of Arts & Science, 1966-1968 (Box 53, Folder 51)
  - Evening Division, 1962-1965 (Box 53, Folder 52)
  - Cutler, Max, 1967-1968 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Dansforth Foundation, 1964-1975 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Dansforth Literature & Annual Reports, 1970-1974 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Da Ponte, Marcia, 1975 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Data Processing Unit, 1968-1969 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Chee Davis, 1970 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Dean's Advisory Group, 1974-1975 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Outgoing correspondence, 2000 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Dean's Council Minutes, 1969-1970 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Dean's Council French Study in France, 1970- (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Dean's Council Visiting Committee, 1972- (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Dean's Council Dean's Lecture Series, 1968- (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Deans Council Minutes/Agenda's, 1974-1976 (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Dean's Council Minutes, Agenda, Notes, 1975-, undated (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Dean's Discretionary Fund 8-8570-416, 1971-1973 (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - Dean of Faculty of A & S, 1973- (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Dean's List, 1967-1970 (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - Deanship, WSC, 1968- (Box 53, Folder 19)
  - Dean, Vera, 1961-1967 (Box 53, Folder 20)
  - Debate Team, 1963-1966 (Box 53, Folder 21)
  - Degree Candidates; Graduates, 1971-1972 (Box 53, Folder 22)
  - Degree Program, Three -year, 1971-1972 (Box 53, Folder 23)
  - Ad Hoc Committee on Discipline, 1968-1976 (Box 53, Folder 24)
  - Discipline Policy, 1947-1970 (Box 53, Folder 25)
  - Discipline Policy, 1968-1969 (Box 53, Folder 26)
  - Senate: Discipline Procedures, 1968-1969 (Box 53, Folder 27)
  - Disciplinary Panel Hearings, 1974 (Box 53, Folder 28)
  - Student Disciplinary Proceedings at NYU (adopted by Senate 11/12/1970) (Box 53, Folder 29)
  - Disruption, 1968-1970 (Box 53, Folder 30)
  - Student Disorders: Analysis, 1969 (Box 53, Folder 31)
  - Distinctive Roll, 1963 (Box 53, Folder 32)
  - Doctoral Council, New York State, 1974-1975 (Box 53, Folder 33)
  - Distiguished Professorships, 1964-1968 (Box 53, Folder 34)
  - Dow Chemical Corporation, 1968 (Box 53, Folder 35)
  - Draft, 1973 (Box 53, Folder 36)
  - Draft Classification, 1967-1968 (Box 53, Folder 37)
  - Dress, 1964 (Box 53, Folder 38)
  - Dramatic Literature, 1967-1975 (Box 53, Folder 39)
  - Dreyfuss, Camille & Henry Foundation Proposal, 1975 (Box 53, Folder 40)
  - Drugs, 1971 (Box 53, Folder 41)
  - Dual Major, 1967 (Box 53, Folder 42)
  - Duplication of Courses, 1969-1974 (Box 53, Folder 43)
  - E miscellaneous, 1964-1969 (Box 53, Folder 44)
  - Education Policy Committee Reports, 1963-1967 (Box 53, Folder 45)
  - Education Professions Development Act, 1965-1970 (Box 53, Folder 46)
  - Early Decisions at NYU Medical, 1973 (Box 53, Folder 47)
  - Economics, 1966-1975 (Box 53, Folder 48)
  - Enviromental Science and Engineering Group, 1969 (Box 53, Folder 49)
  - Econmics Brochure, 1975 (Box 53, Folder 50)
  - Evening College of Arts & Science, 1966-1968 (Box 53, Folder 51)
  - Evening Division, 1962-1965 (Box 53, Folder 52)
- Academic Standards Committee; Petitions Committee, 1979-1983 (Box 60, Box 61)
- WSC Faculty Minutes, 1934-1968 (Box 62)